todowebcams.com 2011-05-19

# meeter - Privacy Policy

Preserving your privacy is very important to us. Your privacy is protected while using our Website. Please be sure to read the Website Terms and Conditions.

When you register or submit your user registration application for our Website services, you are required to provide certain personal details, such as your name, e-mail address, city, IP address, user name and password that you use to access our Website, etc.

You can be sure that your personal identification data cannot be accessed or used by other people in order to identify you personally.

We collect all the information and store it in our Customer or User Database.

We may ask the service User for additional information when registering to enter a special event, promotion or offer, contest or survey presented or conducted by us. If the User voluntarily provides us with such information, we will collect it and include it in our User database.

We may also use your personal data to send you information we think may be of interest to you.

Any personal communication sent by any means to us or to any of our Customer Care Service employees, agents or representatives may be included in our User database.

We may use the collected information to improve our marketing campaigns and our services, content and products. We may also send periodic information such as newsletters to our consenting users via e-mail.

We may disclose your personal information under the following circumstances:

> a) for the purposes of complying with the law or enforcing intellectual property rights and other rights, and
> 
> b) the information may be disclosed to third parties if the User is reported or reasonably suspected to have committed a crime using our services.

You expressly authorize us to disclose your personal information in the following cases:

> a) When working with or employing other companies and individuals, we must share with them the user information to provide you with products and services. You will be informed if your information is disclosed to such third parties.
> 
> b) If meeter.com or substantially all or part of its assets are purchased by a third party, meeter.com’s user personal information will be considered an asset that will be transferred to such third party. You acknowledge that such purchase may occur, and that any purchaser of meeter.com may continue to use your Personal Information pursuant to the provisions of the Confidentiality Policy. Any purchase or transfer will be informed through a notice on the meeter.com website.
> 
> c) To enforce the provisions of our Terms of Use and other agreements or to protect the rights, property or safety of meeter.com, our employees, members or others.

We recommend that parents, guardians, and other responsible adults supervise the children’s use of the Internet and other online services as it is possible that they may not fully understand the privacy terms concerning their personal information.

meeter.com may change or update this privacy policy and such changes or updates will be notified to the users through adultmeeter.com. The user will be deemed to have accepted any change 24 hours after notification of such change. If you wish to update or delete your information from our database, please contact our Customer Care Services department through [support@meeter.com](mailto:%20support@meeter.com). – phone + 598 (2) 901 50 64 – fax + 598 (2) 902 75 31
